# **Kaylie Seltenrich**

Junior Web Designer/Full-Stack Developer Calgary, AB - 403-816-9229

Email: kaylie.seltenrich@gmail.com LinkedIn: /in/kavlieseltenrich/ GitHub: KaylieSeltenrich Portfolio: www.kayliesportfolio.ml

#### Overview:

A diligent student currently enrolled in a Full-Stack Development Diploma program with an expected graduation date of December 2020, and previous working experience as a Junior Graphic Designer at Minuteman Press. Strengths include the ability to manage multiple projects efficiently, being a creative problem solver, and having a good visual and artistic sense of design.

## **Skills Summary:**

## **Programming Languages:**

- HTML/HTML5
- JavaScript & Vue.js
- Python

- CSS/CSS3
- Flask

SOL

## Design:

- Illustrator
- Photoshop

Typography & Layout

- InDesign
- CorelDraw

#### **Education:**

#### InnoTech College

June 2020 - December 2020

Calgary, AB

Full-Stack Development Diploma **Projects:** 

- Created a simple HTML/CSS based mobile-responsive website
- Created simple turned-based games (Pokémon battle, Rock/Paper/Scissors) with JavaScript and Vue.js
- Created a Twitter inspired website with Vue, is with ability for user registration, login, and ability to create posts

#### SAIT (Southern Alberta Institute of Technology)

2013 - 2016

Graphic Communications & Print Technology Diploma **Projects:** 

Calgary, AB

- - Completed the design and layout for an entire planner based on the Calgary Stampede (schedules, ads, etc.), as well as a promotional poster
  - Used Illustrator to create original artwork and logos

# **Employment History:**

#### **Minuteman Press South**

April 2017 - December 2017

Junior Graphic Designer/Typesetter

Calgary, AB

- Performed typesetting and design changes to customer files and insured accuracy of information as per client requests and specifications
- Managed multiple projects daily and ensured deadlines were met
- Ensured files were approved and suitable for print
- Designed postcards, certificates, banners, posters, tickets, labels and more

**McDonalds** 2013 - 2014 Front Counter /Cashier Calgary, AB

- Ensured customer satisfaction through courteous communication and accurate placing of orders
- Displayed effective time management skills through handling high customer periods proficiently